Jesus Lopez Averanga

💌 jesus.lopez.averanga@gmail.com 🤰 +591 72016924 👂 Bolivia



Profile

Software developer with knowledges in programming languages such as Javascript, Typescript, Java, PHP. In my last jobs, I worked with MEAN stack to develop administratives projects. I also worked by myself in individual projects with ReactJS library and NextJS framework developing webpages. In database side, I worked with Postgresql, Mysql, Sql server and Mongodb.

Education

Systems Engineering

Feb 2012 - Dec 2017

Universidad Católica Boliviana, La Paz, Bolivia

Employment

Full Stack Developer

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Impuestos Nacionales, La Paz

Worked using technologies: Angular, Spring boot, PostgreSQL.

Software Developer

Feb 2022 - May 2022

Patio de Comidas Zona Sur, La Paz

Worked using technologies: Express.js, Heroku, Node.js, Angular, PostgreSQL.

Software Developer

May 2021 - Dec 2021

Instituto Nacional de Estadística, La Paz

Worked using technologies: PrimeNG, Express.js, Node.js, Angular, PostgreSQL.

Software Developer

Jan 2019 - May 2021

Alianza, Comercio Exportador, La Paz

Worked using technologies: MongoDB, PHP, Express.js, Java, Node.js, Angular.

Courses

Web programming

Nov 2013

Programming languages and database using: Javascript, php, and msql.

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

Personal details

Website

jesus-portfolio.web.app

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jesus-lopaveranga

GitHub

github.com/bowed89

Skills

Javascript

Typescript

Java

PHP

Angular

Reactis

Spring boot

Nodejs

Mysql

Mongodb

Postgress

TailwindCSS

Web design
Course based on html, css, dreamweaver.

Database
Course based on sql server.

MEAN stack application development
Course based on development of an application using javascript technologies of MEAN stack.

Languages
English

French